<resources>
    
    <string name="app_name">DinoKids</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">About</string>
    <string name="aboutAuthor">Daniel Flores professional Android developer</string>
    <string name="resource">http://www.sciencekids.co.nz/pictures/dinosaurs.html</string>

    <string-array name="dinosaursNames">
        <item>Achelousaurus</item>
        <item>Allosaurus</item>
        <item>Centrosaurus </item>
        <item>Spinosaurus </item>
        <item>Utahraptor </item>
        <item>Rajasaurus </item>
        <item>Albertosaurus</item>
        <item> Avaceratops </item>
        <item> Anchiceratops </item>
        <item>Nipponosaurus </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="dinosaursDescription">
        <item> Dinosaur from the late Cretaceous Period (around 80 million years ago)
            that lived in what is now North America. Achelousaurus was a herbivore that
            reached around 6 metres (20 feet) in length and featured two distinct horns
            coming from its neck frill. It was named in 1995 by paleontologist Scott Sampson.</item>

        <item> Dinosaur from the late Jurassic Period (around 150 million years ago).
            First described back in 1877, Allosaurus become one of the first well known dinosaurs.
            It was a carnivore (meat eater) and weighed around 2.3 tons.</item>

        <item> Stocky dinosaur from the late Cretaceous Period (around 76 million years ago).
            The name Centrosaurus means pointed \'lizard\' and refers to the small points found
            along the frill of the dinosaur. Remains of the Centrosaurus have been found in Alberta, Canada.</item>

        <item> Dinosaur from the Cretaceous Period (around 100 million years ago).
            With huge spines growing from its back and the biggest size of any meat eating (carnivorous) dinosaur,
            the Spinosaurus must have been one scary looking dinosaur.</item>

        <item> Dinosaur from the early Cretaceous Period (around 124 million years ago).
            The Utahraptor is a Theropod from a family of dinosaurs called Dromaeosauridae
            (more commonly known as raptors). The Utahraptor is the largest known member of this family
            with scientists estimating it could have reached a length of 7 metres (23 feet).
            Utahraptor fossils were first found in the US state of Utah in 1991.</item>

        <item> Rajasaurus (which interestingly means \'prince\' or \'princely lizard\'),
            a dinosaur from the late Cretaceous Period (around 70 million years ago).
            Found in India, it featured a unique head crest and measured around 8 metres (26 feet) in length.</item>

        <item> Dinosaur from the late Cretaceous Period.
            Albertosaurus was a predator that moved on two legs,
            living in an area that now makes up western North America.
            While smaller than other Tyrannosaurids such as the well known Tyrannosaurus rex,
            Albertosaurus still grew to a length of up to 9 metres (30 feet) and a weight of around 1.4 tons.</item>

        <item> Dinosaur from the late Cretaceous Period. The first fossil remains of Avaceratops were found in 1981 in Montana,
            USA. Like other Ceratopsian dinosaurs, Avaceratops was a herbivore (plant eater).</item>

        <item> Dinosaur from the late Cretaceous Period (around 70 million years ago).
            Anchiceratops was a herbivore (plant eater) that walked on four legs and featured three horns on its face (much like other Ceratopsids).
            Named in 1914, Anchiceratops reached up to 6 metres (20 feet) in length and lived in what is now western North America.</item>

        <item> Nipponosaurus (meaning \'Japanese lizard\'), a dinosaur from the late Cretaceous Period.
            Fossils of the Nipponsaurus were first found in Japan in 1934.</item>

    </string-array>
</resources>
